<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Alon Wolf</title>
    <link>https://a10nw01f.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Alon Wolf</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://a10nw01f.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Live DLL Reloading</title>
      <link>https://a10nw01f.github.io/live_dll_reloading/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://a10nw01f.github.io/live_dll_reloading/</guid>
      <description>Live DLL Reloading Iteration time is very important for development and debugging. Usually, in order to see the effect of a change in code we need to close the process, compile a new version, start the process again and then reach a specific part or scenario in the program - this entire flow can be very slow. DLL live reloading can decrease iteration times by replacing an old DLL with a new one during runtime without even closing the process so that we can observe the changes almost immediatly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Generative C&#43;&#43;</title>
      <link>https://a10nw01f.github.io/generative_cpp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://a10nw01f.github.io/generative_cpp/</guid>
      <description>Code Generation in C++ The two main ways to generate code in c++ are templates and macros. While macros can manipulate text they lack the compile time information and constraints that the compiler provides. Templates on the other hand are incredibly powerful especially with c++20&amp;rsquo;s concepts, non type template parameters and increased constexpr support, however they still lack the ability to manipulate strings such as identifiers and keywords.
Metaclasses A proposal by Herb Sutter to add metaclasses to the c++ language.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
